Guide to the Edward G. and Hortense R. Levy Autograph Collection, Part Two
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Autograph Items by Category, 1666-1961; Series I; 12.1; (32 boxes)
  - THEATER
    - Saxon, Edwin F., 1893-1894 (Box 32, Folder 1660)
    - Scott, Margaret Clement, undated (Box 32, Folder 1661)
    - Shakespeare Memorial Association, 1897 (Box 32, Folder 1662)
    - Simpson, J. Palgrave (John Palgrave), 1807-1887, 1848 (Box 32, Folder 1663)
    - Smith, Albert, 1816-1860, undated (Box 32, Folder 1664)
    - Sothern, Edward Askew, 1826-1881, undated (Box 32, Folder 1665)
    - Stirling, Fanny, 1815-1895, undated (Box 32, Folder 1666)
    - Taylor, Henry, Sir, 1800-1886, undated (Box 32, Folder 1667)
    - Terriss, William, 1852-1897, 1883 (Box 32, Folder 1668)
    - Terry, Ellen, Dame, 1847-1928, 1891 (Box 32, Folder 1669)
    - Terry, Fred, 1864-1933 and Neilson, Julia, b 1868, undated (Box 32, Folder 1670)
    - Theatre Royal, lease, 1872 (Box 32, Folder 1671)
    - Tree, Herbert Beerbohm, Sir, 1853-1917, 1898 (Box 32, Folder 1672)
    - Unidentified, 1835 (Box 32, Folder 1673)
    - Unidentified theatre, playbill, undated (Box 32, Folder 1674)
    - Vanbrugh, Irene, Dame, 1872-1949, undated (Box 32, Folder 1675)
    - Vanbrugh, Violet, 1867-1942, 1904 (Box 32, Folder 1676)
    - Vezin, Jane Elizabeth, 1827-1902, undated (Box 32, Folder 1677)
    - Vokes, Jessie, 1851-1884, 1879 (Box 32, Folder 1678)
    - Wallack, Henry John, 1790-1870 and Wallack, James William, 1791?-1864, 1848 (Box 32, Folder 1679)
    - Ward, Genevieve, 1838-1922, undated (Box 32, Folder 1680)
    - Welch, James, 1900 (Box 32, Folder 1681)
    - Willard, Edward, 1853-1915, undated (Box 32, Folder 1682)
    - Williams, Francis, b. 1854, 1912 (Box 32, Folder 1683)
    - Zion Hall, programme, undated (Box 32, Folder 1684)
- Uncategorized Autograph Items and Fragments, 1697-1942; Series II; 1.67; (4 boxes)
  Series II, Other Autographs, contains autograph items collected by the Levys but unarranged by them. Many of these are fragments; some carry illegible signatures. In many cases, they seem to be items that originally accompanied other manuscript purchases by the Levys and were set aside for later identification and classification. Where possible, these items have been roughly sorted alphabetically by name of signer. Unidentified and fragmentary materials are filed in box 36 at the end of the alphabetical run.
  - A (Box 33, Folder 1685-1687)
  - B (Box 33, Folder 1688-1691)
  - C (Box 33, Folder 1692-1695)
  - D (Box 33, Folder 1696-1697)
  - E (Box 33, Folder 1698)
  - F (Box 33, Folder 1699)
  - G (Box 34, Folder 1700-1701)
  - H (Box 34, Folder 1702-1704)
  - J (Box 34, Folder 1705)
  - K (Box 34, Folder 1706)
  - L (Box 34, Folder 1707-1708)
  - M (Box 34, Folder 1709-1711)
  - N (Box 35, Folder 1712)
  - O (Box 35, Folder 1713)
  - P (Box 35, Folder 1714)
  - R (Box 35, Folder 1715-1716)
  - S (Box 35, Folder 1717-1719)
  - T (Box 35, Folder 1720-1721)
  - U (Box 35, Folder 1722)
  - V (Box 35, Folder 1723)
  - W (Box 35, Folder 1724-1725)
  - X, Y and Z, 1833-1906 (Box 36, Folder 1726)
  - Unidentified and fragments, circa 1780-1900 (Box 36, Folder 1727-1728)
- Lists, 1950-1975; Series III; 0.83; (2 boxes)
  Series III, Lists, contains unsorted copies of lists of autograph material.
  - Lists, circa 1950-75 (Box 37, Folder 1729-1734)
  - Lists, circa 1950-75 (Box 38, Folder 1735-1738)